Guide to the Whitman College Dean of Students records
Whitman College and Northwest Archives
- Office of Student Affairs, 1948-2009
  - Council on Student Affairs: Meeting minutes and memoranda [Folder restricted until 2046], 1960-1971 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Council on Student Affairs: Meeting minutes and records [Folder restricted until 2044], 1965-1969 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Council on Student Affairs: Minutes [Folder restricted until 2031], 1954-1956 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Council on Student Affairs: Minutes [Folder restricted until 2033], 1956-1958 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Council on Student Affairs: Minutes [Folder restricted until 2035], 1958-1960 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Council on Student Affairs: Minutes [Folder restricted until 2037], 1960-1962 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Council on Student Affairs: Minutes [Folder restricted until 2039], 1962-1964 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Council on Student Affairs: Minutes [Folder restricted until 2040], 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Council on Student Affairs: Minutes [Folder restricted until 2042], 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Council on Student Affairs: Minutes [Folder restricted until 2041], 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Council on Student Affairs: Student-Faculty discipline committee minutes [Folder restricted until 2029], 1951-1954 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Council on Student Affairs: Petition to change practice of publicly posting disciplinary actions, circa 1960 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Council on Student Affairs: Policy manual, 1944-1977 (Box 20)
  - Council on Student Affairs: Statement and memoranda on disturbances in residence halls, 1977 December 1 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Establishment of the Office of Student Affairs, memoranda and organization charts, 1948, bulk 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - [Excused absences and] Chaperones, 1951-1956 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Council correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Freshman handbook [memoranda], 1956-1959 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Freshman handbook supplement [Continuing Orientation and Related Education Committee (CORE)], circa 1950-1970 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Food services, 1991-1993 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Group scholastic ratings, 1971 November-1978 June (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Health Center [administration (staffing and assessment)], 1 of 2, 1985-1994 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Health Center [administration (staffing and assessment)], 2 of 2, 1985-1994 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Health Center, contract letters, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Health Center, medical records information [Folder restricted until 2064], 1973-1989 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Health Center, emergencies, 1978-1982 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Legal aspects of student discipline, 1 of 2, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Legal aspects of student discipline, 2 of 2, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Letter to students living off-campus, student social regulations, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Meeting minutes, Student Personnel Services and Office of Student Affairs, 1976 September 10-1977 April 15 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Memorandum from Faculty Council to Student Congress concerning "Study Firesides" petition, 1963-03-01T00:00:00+00:00 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Multicultural student affairs, 1 of 2 [Partial contents restricted until 2067], 1988-1993 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Multicultural student affairs, 2 of 2 [Partial contents restricted until 2067], 1988-1993 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Multicultural student affairs, Director job search, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Multicultural student affairs, posters, circa 1988-1993 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Office of Activities, 1962 July 27-1993 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Office of Student Affairs case study, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Office restructuring meeting minutes, job descriptions and duties, annual reports, 1961-1964, bulk 1978 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Petition for senior women curfew extension, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Policy manual, Dean of Women, 1 of 3, 1950-1967 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Policy manual, Dean of Women, 2 of 3, 1950-1967 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Policy manual, Dean of Women, 3 of 3, 1950-1967 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Senior class constitution, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Senior womens' privileges, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Social regulations: legal, drugs, et cetera [and students' rights and freedoms] [Partial contents restricted until 2048], 1970-1973 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Student activities record forms, 1985-1992 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Student center, 1 of 2, 1980-1993 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Student center, 2 of 2, 1980-1993 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Student congress letter to [faculty], 1963 May (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Student employment [Partial contents restricted until 2067], 1985-1992 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Student education records, 1972-1993 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Students' rights and freedoms, circa 1991 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Student Services: A Look at Student Services Budgets 1977-1978 to 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Student Services: Academic Resource Center, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Student Services annual report, 1990-1993 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Student Services: Breakaways, 1993-1998 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Student Services: Budget projections, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Student Services: Career Center internships, 2008-2009 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Student Services: Correspondence with student services administrators at other colleges, 1989-1993 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Student Services: Counseling Center statistical reports, 1985-1996 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Student Services: Food Service, 1986-1994 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Student Services: Goals statements, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Student Services: Goals statements, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Student Services: Goals statements, 1990-1993 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Student Services: Health Center evaluation, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Student Services: Health Center statistical reports, 1987-1991 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Student Services: Health Center statistical reports, 1991-1993 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Student Services: Health Center statistical reports, 1993-1995 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Student Services: Job descriptions, 1 of 3, 1978-1993 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Student Services: Job descriptions, 2 of 3, 1978-1993 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Student Services: Job descriptions, 3 of 3, 1978-1993 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Student Services: Job descriptions, 1991-1996 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Student Services: Job descriptions, 1993-1996 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Student Services: Memoranda, 1989-1994 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Student Services: Organizational charts, 1978-1985 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Student Services: Organizational charts, 1978-1995 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Student Services: Professional staff evaluations [blank forms], 1979-1990 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Student Services: Staff evaluations forms [blank forms], 1982 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Student Services: Retreat, 1989-1991 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Student Services: Retreat, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Student Services: Retreat, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Student Services: Retreat, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Student Services: Retreat, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Student Services: Retreat, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Student Services staff [Partial contents restricted until 2069], 1980-1997 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Student Services: Staff evaluation guidelines, 1976-1981 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Student Services: Staff meetings, 1982-1995 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Student Services: Staff meetings, 1990-1995 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Student Services: Student review board, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Student Services: Student Union, 1986-1989 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Student Services: Student Union, 1993-1996 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Student Services: Study groups, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Student Services: Study resources center [Partial contents restricted until 2067], 1979-1990 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Student Services: [Summer] calendar, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Student Services: Study Resources Center, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Student Services: Summer conferences, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Student Services: Study Resources Center, Student Services: Summer language project, 1980-1985 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Student Services: Summer dance lab [Partial contents restricted until 2070], 1980-1995 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Student Services: Summer programs, 1981-1993 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Student Services: Tutors, 1984-1993 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Student Services: Visions, 1985 September (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Student Services: Voter registration, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Student Services: Women [Women's Resource Center], 1986-1996 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Student Services: Writing lab, 1981-1993 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Union-Bulletin article on Office of Student Affairs reorganization, 1978-05-29; Office of Student Affairs (Box 16, Folder 14)